Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions Records 6324
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions Records
1996-2011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions
Labor Management Partnership
6324
3.89 cubic feet
3.9 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements, audio visual materials.
7301271
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 18, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6324 AV: Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions Audio-Visual Materials
Collective labor agreements; Health facilities -- Employees -- Labor unions; Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Union
7301271
- Power of Partnership: Changing Our Jobs (Video One) and The Genesis (Bonus Video), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  VHS video cassette
- Power of Partnership: Changing Our Jobs (Video One) and The Genesis (Bonus Video), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  VHS video cassette. Copy 2.
- AFT LMP Presentation, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Kathy Schmidt and Anthony Gately, April 20, 2001, Washington, DC
- Bargaining (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Certification Task Force Recommendations, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Foundation Building Outside KPNW, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- IUD Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- IUD Kaiser Analysis, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Inside Out Newsletter, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  v.1:no.1 (1998:Fall)
- Interest-Based Bargaining, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Kaiser Permanente AFL-CIO Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions: The Bargaining Task Group [folder 1 of 2], 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Kaiser Permanente AFL-CIO Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions: The Bargaining Task Group [folder 2 of 2], 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Kaiser Permanente AFL-CIO Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions: The Common Issues Bargaining Recommendations [folder 1 of 4], 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Kaiser Permanente AFL-CIO Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions: The Common Issues Bargaining Recommendations [folder 2 of 4], 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Kaiser Permanente AFL-CIO Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions: The Common Issues Bargaining Recommendations [folder 3 of 4], 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Kaiser Permanente AFL-CIO Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions: The Common Issues Bargaining Recommendations [folder 4 of 4], 2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Kaiser Permanente AFL-CIO Labor Management Partnership: 2003-2005 Implementation Plan (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Draft revised March 6, 2003
- Kaiser Permanente AFL-CIO Partnership in the Northwest Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- LM Conference Presentation, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Peter diCicco and Judith Saunders
- LMP Pathways to Partnership, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- LMP Root Learning Maps, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- LMP Union Education Program, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- MIT Research Proposal, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Meetings of the Kaiser Permanente Medical Care Organizations Board of Directors [folder 1 of 3], 2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Quality and Health Improvement Committee, April 29, 2004
- Meetings of the Kaiser Permanente Medical Care Organizations Board of Directors [folder 2 of 3], 2004 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Meetings of the Kaiser Permanente Medical Care Organizations Board of Directors [folder 3 of 3], 2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- "The NLRB Box" Presentation, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Peter diCicco, April 29, 2001
- National Agreement Deliverables, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- National Agreement Press, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- National Contract, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- National LMP Leadership Conference, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  December 2-3, 2003
- National Partnership Council, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Organizers' Conference, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Conference folder. Chicago, IL, September 25, 1998. 2 copies
- Originals OFTEHP Convention, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Partnership, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Partnerhsip Proposal, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Privileges of Partnership (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Quality Sub-Committee, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- RAI NPC LMP Orientation, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Rollout Materials, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Root Learning Maps, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- SPC Sub-Committee, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- SPC Minutes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- SPC Minutes, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Senior Partnership Council, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Strategy Group, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Structure Task Force, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- United Bargaining: Collective Bargain Workgroup, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Workforce Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Flex/MLK, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- NCAL Office of Labor Management Partnership Guide, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Workforce Development, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Attendance, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Georgia, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Ciat, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Texas, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Georgia, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- SIPTU 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Connected for Health, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- National Sabor College/KP, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- UBT EducTools, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Sweden, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Reg Rate of Pay, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Kaiser Permanente, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Self Funding, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- John, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Financial Statements, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Calibre CPA, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Participative Governance, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Kaiser Permanente Retirement Plans Investment Committee Meeting 2010 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Kaiser Permanente Retirement Plans Investment Committee Meeting 2011 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Kaiser Strategy Group Meeting 2006 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- LMP Attendance Engagement Model Field Guide, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Guide to Integration Partnership at the Work Unit Level, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- LMP Joint Marketing Implementation Tool Kit, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- LMPT Monthly Financial Package Six Monthes Ended Folder 1, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- LMPT Monthly Financial Statement Package for the Six Months Ended, Folder 2, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Talking About Attendance / Southern California LMP Regional Council (Box 4)
  - Talking About Attendance / Southern California LMP Regional Council (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Turning Great ideas Ino Great Results / Unit-Based Teams (June 2007) (Box 5)
  - Turning Great Ideas Into Great Results / Unit-Based Teams, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    June 2007
- Eleanor Roosevelt Awards, Lon O'Neil, Asela Espiritu (Box 6)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Awards Lon O'Neil, Asela Espiritu, 4/18/2007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Credit: Jay Mallin / American Rights at Work
- Labor Management Partnership (Box 7)
  - Labor Management Partnership (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Includes PDF of LMP Implementation Plan material; PowerPoint presentation; and ordering information
- Power Point: Not Business as usual KP's Labor Management Partnership (Box 8)
  - Power Point: not business as usual KP's Labor Management Partnership (Box 8, Folder 1)
- LMPT - 06/2009 Financials (Box 9)
  - LMPT - 06/2009 Financials (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Asela Espiritu - Worker panel with Whitford & Mathis (Box 10)
  - Asela Espiritu - Worker panel with Whitford + Mathis (Box 10, Folder 1)
    credit: Jay Mallin/American Rights at Work
- Talking About Attendance / Southern California LMP REgional Council (Box 11)
  - Talking About Attendance / Southern California LMP Regional Council (Box 11, Folder 1)